export const sommen = [
    { question: "12 + 9", correct: 21, options: [21, 19, 22, 24], poses: ["tree", "warrior", "pray", "curve"] },
    { question: "35 - 17", correct: 18, options: [16, 18, 20, 22], poses: ["stretch", "pull", "curve", "pray"] },
    { question: "8 x 6", correct: 48, options: [42, 48, 54, 46], poses: ["warrior", "tree", "stretch", "pull"] },
    { question: "100 - 47", correct: 53, options: [51, 53, 55, 50], poses: ["pray", "curve", "pull", "stretch"] },
    { question: "25 + 36", correct: 61, options: [61, 63, 59, 65], poses: ["tree", "curve", "pull", "warrior"] },
    { question: "9 x 7", correct: 63, options: [56, 63, 72, 67], poses: ["stretch", "tree", "pray", "curve"] },
    { question: "81 - 29", correct: 52, options: [50, 52, 54, 48], poses: ["pull", "pray", "tree", "warrior"] },
    { question: "17 + 12", correct: 29, options: [27, 29, 31, 32], poses: ["stretch", "warrior", "pray", "tree"] },
    { question: "14 x 4", correct: 56, options: [54, 56, 58, 60], poses: ["pull", "curve", "pray", "warrior"] },
    { question: "77 - 24", correct: 53, options: [51, 53, 55, 52], poses: ["tree", "pull", "stretch", "warrior"] },
    { question: "20 + 16", correct: 36, options: [36, 38, 34, 40], poses: ["tree", "warrior", "stretch", "curve"] },
    { question: "5 x 9", correct: 45, options: [42, 45, 48, 47], poses: ["pull", "curve", "stretch", "pray"] },
    { question: "89 - 33", correct: 56, options: [54, 56, 58, 60], poses: ["warrior", "pray", "pull", "tree"] },
    { question: "13 + 8", correct: 21, options: [21, 23, 25, 20], poses: ["stretch", "curve", "tree", "warrior"] },
    { question: "6 x 7", correct: 42, options: [40, 42, 44, 45], poses: ["pull", "tree", "stretch", "warrior"] },
    { question: "32 + 18", correct: 50, options: [49, 50, 51, 52], poses: ["warrior", "pray", "tree", "curve"] },
    { question: "19 + 15", correct: 34, options: [32, 34, 36, 38], poses: ["stretch", "pull", "warrior", "tree"] },
    { question: "72 - 29", correct: 43, options: [41, 43, 45, 47], poses: ["curve", "pray", "warrior", "tree"] },
    { question: "4 x 8", correct: 32, options: [30, 32, 34, 36], poses: ["warrior", "pray", "pull", "tree"] },
    { question: "63 - 48", correct: 15, options: [13, 15, 17, 19], poses: ["pull", "tree", "warrior", "stretch"] },
    { question: "18 + 26", correct: 44, options: [42, 44, 46, 48], poses: ["tree", "warrior", "stretch", "pray"] },
    { question: "7 x 8", correct: 56, options: [54, 56, 58, 60], poses: ["pull", "curve", "stretch", "pray"] },
    { question: "100 - 36", correct: 64, options: [62, 64, 66, 68], poses: ["tree", "warrior", "stretch", "curve"] },
    { question: "23 + 39", correct: 62, options: [60, 62, 64, 66], poses: ["tree", "curve", "pull", "warrior"] },
    { question: "11 x 9", correct: 99, options: [97, 99, 101, 103], poses: ["pray", "curve", "stretch", "warrior"] },
    { question: "42 - 17", correct: 25, options: [23, 25, 27, 29], poses: ["tree", "warrior", "pray", "curve"] },
    { question: "28 + 33", correct: 61, options: [59, 61, 63, 65], poses: ["stretch", "pull", "tree", "warrior"] },
    { question: "24 x 5", correct: 120, options: [118, 120, 122, 124], poses: ["curve", "pray", "pull", "warrior"] },
    { question: "56 + 12", correct: 68, options: [66, 68, 70, 72], poses: ["tree", "curve", "stretch", "pray"] },
    { question: "75 - 36", correct: 39, options: [37, 39, 41, 43], poses: ["warrior", "tree", "stretch", "pull"] },
    { question: "13 x 5", correct: 65, options: [62, 64, 65, 67], poses: ["stretch", "warrior", "curve", "pull"] },
    { question: "50 + 22", correct: 72, options: [70, 72, 74, 76], poses: ["tree", "pull", "curve", "stretch"] },
    { question: "9 x 8", correct: 72, options: [70, 72, 74, 76], poses: ["warrior", "tree", "stretch", "pray"] },
    { question: "36 + 45", correct: 81, options: [79, 81, 83, 85], poses: ["pray", "tree", "stretch", "warrior"] },
    { question: "14 x 3", correct: 42, options: [40, 42, 44, 46], poses: ["tree", "curve", "warrior", "pull"] },
    { question: "90 - 53", correct: 37, options: [35, 37, 39, 41], poses: ["stretch", "pray", "pull", "warrior"] },
    { question: "63 + 18", correct: 81, options: [79, 81, 83, 85], poses: ["pull", "curve", "stretch", "warrior"] },
    { question: "40 + 32", correct: 72, options: [70, 72, 74, 76], poses: ["tree", "stretch", "warrior", "pull"] },
    { question: "54 - 23", correct: 31, options: [29, 31, 33, 35], poses: ["warrior", "tree", "stretch", "pray"] },
    { question: "48 + 37", correct: 85, options: [83, 85, 87, 89], poses: ["stretch", "pull", "tree", "warrior"] },
    { question: "8 x 9", correct: 72, options: [70, 72, 74, 76], poses: ["tree", "stretch", "warrior", "curve"] },
    { question: "25 + 42", correct: 67, options: [65, 67, 69, 71], poses: ["stretch", "pull", "curve", "pray"] },
    { question: "5 x 12", correct: 60, options: [58, 60, 62, 64], poses: ["warrior", "tree", "pull", "curve"] },
    { question: "62 + 28", correct: 90, options: [88, 90, 92, 94], poses: ["tree", "pull", "stretch", "warrior"] },
    { question: "7 x 9", correct: 63, options: [61, 63, 65, 67], poses: ["curve", "tree", "warrior", "pray"] },
    { question: "50 + 25", correct: 75, options: [73, 75, 77, 79], poses: ["warrior", "tree", "stretch", "pull"] },
    { question: "43 + 12", correct: 55, options: [53, 55, 57, 59], poses: ["stretch", "warrior", "pull", "tree"] },
    { question: "72 - 34", correct: 38, options: [36, 38, 40, 42], poses: ["tree", "stretch", "warrior", "curve"] },
    { question: "9 + 18", correct: 27, options: [25, 27, 29, 31], poses: ["stretch", "pull", "warrior", "tree"] },
    { question: "64 + 28", correct: 92, options: [90, 92, 94, 96], poses: ["tree", "warrior", "pull", "pray" ]}
]
